infoaxe.com 2014-12-10

# Flipora - Terms of Service and Privacy Policy

* * *

**Flipora** is a product by Infoaxe Inc.

Flipora, a product from Infoaxe, solves two big problems for users.

  * Discovery: Bored on the Web? You'll never be anymore. Flipora recommends great websites to you automatically on topics you care about. Discover the freshest, most interesting websites of the day that are automatically recommended to you based on what like minded people enjoy each day.

  * Web History Search: Full text web browsing history search that's fast and efficient. You never have to waste time bookmarking or tagging pages that you want to get back to. Flipora automatically saves all the webpages you browse and makes it searchable from any computer or browser.

**We value the privacy of our users and will never sell or rent your email address to third parties.**

We advise that this software should only be installed by Users aged eighteen (18) and over. We don't deliver any adult content as a result of installing our software.

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the Flipora website and services, post a link to the Flipora website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. We may store some information on the third party data analytics services which we use for our analytics but Unless required by law, we will not share our users' browsing and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or in anonymous form, with third parties. Flipora may send you updates & notifications from other members by email, but will never sell or rent your email address to third parties. You will not send email invitations to non-users without their consent. You will not send unsolicited messages to other users. Failure to adhere to the terms outlined here will lead to suspension of your account.

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive. The user's information will not be supplemented with information from other sources.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website. We will notify the users through email when a Material Change has been made to the EULA, Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, etc. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with Flipora, you can send an e-mail, in English please, to support@infoaxe.com.

If you would like access to your personal information to correct, update, or delete it, please contact us at [support@flipora.com](mailto:support@flipora.com).

Infoaxe is located at 440 N Wolfe Rd MS#153, Sunnyvale, CA 94085. You can cancel your Flipora account, unsubscribe from all emails by following the instructions here. To uninstall the addon, follow the instructions [here](http://blog.flipora.com/2013/12/06/how-to-uninstall-flipora/).

Infoaxe Inc's application Flipora 2.0 is certified as a Trusted Download Program by TRUSTe signifying that the Flipora application has been tested by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe's TDP program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding the Flipora application, please contact us at Infoaxe Inc., 440 N Wolfe Rd MS#153, Sunnyvale, CA 94085 or by email at [support@flipora.com](mailto:support@flipora.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe [here](http://clicktoverify.truste.com/pvr.php?page=validate&softwareProgramId=510&sealid=112). The TRUSTe Trusted Download program covers only Flipora application and does not cover other applications such as mobile versions, Facebook or Twitter apps.

For issues/questions email [support@flipora.com](mailto:support@flipora.com).
